There seems to be like a floor in the
market where market comes down there's
always a buyer at some point.
>> What's the floor now?
>> So this is a phenomenon that happens.
Bitcoin price is very much driven by a
number of factors. On the one hand you
have global liquidity. Every country is
starting to issue more debt. It's not
just the US. And so global liquidity is
growing rapidly. Bitcoin tends to lag
into by about 90 days.
>> There's this narrative that retails
believe miners have the power to control
Bitcoin price especially around having.
Is it true? I think
>> do you think it makes sense to have a
national Bitcoin miner run by the
government now that we have a Bitcoin
strategic reserve? If I were a
government and I have a mandate, an
executive order now to collect Bitcoin
in a strategic reserve.
>> I think we are within 2 years of a time
where energy companies truly on a global
scale become partners with Bitcoin
mining. You'll see a $10,000 drop in
Bitcoin. We have been outperforming
Micro Strategy.
>> Your stock should perform like a Bitcoin
treasury.
>> It does actually, which is a bad thing
because there are three constraints in
the Bitcoin mining business. We own the
three C's, capital, compute, and
capacity.
>> What do you think caused the price
oppression of Mara stock as well as some
other miners year to date relative to
Bitcoin?
>> I think with positive luck.
>> What does that mean?
>> So, statistically speaking, if you have
1% of global hash rate, you should earn
1% of the blocks.
>> We earn a little bit more than that.
>> How?
>> The difficulty only changes every 2
weeks. If you're very efficient, you can
swap what your miners are doing from one
block to another block if a block is
near being solved and you don't think
you will solve it. Oh, try to change the
21 million cap. Is it possible?
>> Um,
[Music]
>> Fred Teal returns to the show. He is a
CEO of Marathon Digital Holdings, one of
the largest Bitcoin miners in America,
if not the world. I'm David Lynn. Bonnie
Chang
>> and we're here to discuss Fred's outlook
for the entire Bitcoin space, including
mining. An honor to host you, Fred. It's
very rare we have the opportunity to
talk to a very large minor like
yourself. So, thank you for joining the
program.
>> Great to be here.
>> Let's just follow up on the conversation
we had last time on the show. I mean,
Bitcoin was at an all-time high, Ben.
It's at a new all-time high now. Uh the
strategic reserve is now signed to
executive action. What is the next
catalyst for the new all-time high
that's coming up next inevitably
hopefully? Well,
>> I think uh a couple of things. For one
thing, we're seeing all these Bitcoin
treasury companies being created.
>> Yeah. Um, so where Michael Sailor before
was kind of the person in town buying
900 Bitcoin a day for his own
admissions, you now have the Trump
family, you have uh Caner Fitzgerald um
together with Tether and you have many
others who all are raising
multi-billions of dollars who are going
to be in the market competing with
Michael Sailor to buy Bitcoin which is
essentially going to drive number go up.
um I think for a period of time um
stable corn legislation passing through
Congress and landing on the president's
desk uh I think is going to be another
small leg up. Then you have market
structure uh soon behind that and then
you have the strategic Bitcoin reserve
um coming as number three. The SB uh
right now based on what I understand
from the White House the SB is now
they'll be receiving reports from all
the government departments. So,
Treasury, etc. on how much Bitcoin the
government actually holds. More than
likely, it'll be a number in the 100,000
range because uh you have to think of
forfeite laws. And while the FBI or uh
IRS may have confiscated Bitcoin, it may
not be theirs to actually hold. There
may be a victim that they have to
deliver it to. Um and so you must
probably have about 100,000 Bitcoin
uh that they have. The question is then
what is uh the administration going to
do to add to it and what revenue neutral
programs are they going to do to do
that? And I think the US um needs to
move quickly because you now have other
nation states wanting to do Bitcoin
strategic reserves and if they start
buying Bitcoin ahead of the US then it's
kind of well the US you guys were first
but you haven't done anything about it.
So I think uh when the US announces
they're actually buying or adding to the
Bitcoin reserve, that'll be another
catalyst. So you have a multitude of
steps. Um you're seeing some great
inflows into ETFs right now, which is
primarily retail. Um but you're also
starting to see more and more
institutional buying. You know, there's
a definite I think you and I have talked
about this before. There seems to be
like a floor in the market where
>> market comes down. There's always a
buyer
>> at some point.
>> What's the floor now? Um, you know,
right now I think um there's very strong
support at 98. Um, we're building
support at 106
and you know, we hit 110, we bounced
down to 108, we hit 110 a little bit
more, we bounced down to 108. So I think
106 is pretty good support. Um, and a
back stop to that is 98.
>> So 450 new bitcoins are mined every
single day. But all the people or
companies or governments that are trying
to buy Bitcoin sounds like they're
trying to buy a lot. But Bitcoin price
does not really reflect on the type of
demand that we are talking about. Why?
>> So you're seeing long-term holders and
this is a phenomenon that happens always
when you have 98% of Bitcoin in profit.
Then what you end up having is people
start selling. The long-term holders at
this stage in the market cycle typically
sell a portion of their Bitcoin with a
plan of buying it back when Bitcoin
drops again. Um, I don't think we're in
a cycle like we've ever seen before. And
so I would love for them to be proven
wrong and then have to come in to the
market again while Bitcoin is rallying
at 120, 130. Um, so I think it's it's a
different market today uh than what
they're used to seeing. But when you
have this much Bitcoin in profit, people
feel, "Okay, maybe I should sell a
little, take some chips off the table
and uh buy on the dip when it comes back
down." We'll see.
>> Is a dip going to be lower than 100k.
>> Uh it's hard to tell. Um Bitcoin price
is very much driven by a number of
factors. On the one hand, you have
global liquidity, M2 money supply,
especially the asset side of that. And
if you have um a lot of government
spending going on, a lot of liquidity
coming to the market. I mean, China
central bank globally, every country is
starting to issue more debt. Um it's not
just the US. And so global liquidity is
growing rapidly. Bitcoin tends to lag M2
by about 90 days typically. Um, but you
have these little foibless like Trump
could decide on a new tariff policy and
then you'll see the market drop or he
may remove tariffs altogether and the
market will go up. So you have these uh
I call it policy changes that can affect
the price of Bitcoin. Um you have also
portfolio adjustments right where you
have people who have previously been uh
in equities who now sell equities go
into bond portfolios and as they releet
their portfolios what ends up happening
is you know Bitcoin is an allocation of
their portfolio and if they decide
they're going to rebalance to or from
Bitcoin or they're just liquidating a
certain portion to go into cash because
they want to go in and buy something
else uh then they'll liquidate across
their portfolio. potentially. And so
those are the things that drive these
dips. Um the big dips, the 20% dips, uh
those are more macro. Um you know, the
Fed decides that we're not going to cut
interest rates at all. You'll see a
$10,000 drop in Bitcoin on something
like that. Um so it's very much a the
news is driving the price right now,
unfortunately. Um but I think over time
uh there's just so much more demand than
supply and uh you know as the number
keeps edging its way up uh you know you
think about last year we went through
this period where we were kind of moving
sideways for a long period of time and
then there was a dip and then boom
bounce up and then now we were up at a
new level right and uh think about it
July of last year we were bouncing in
the $50,000 range and then all of a
sudden it was 70 and then all of a
sudden it was 90 right and then we We're
at 100 just after election day. So, um I
think we're going to see that type of
volatility
uh continue. But what's interesting is
that you look at the volatility curve
and we're really starting to see a
flattening on a logarithmic scale
>> of the volatility curve of Bitcoin. And
if you look at the power law and you
look at some of these other methods
people use for evaluating Bitcoin price,
I think what you're going to see is that
um the volatility in Bitcoin is starting
to diminish.
Don't know what that does to its
attractiveness in the market anymore.
But the more stable Bitcoin becomes, the
more like gold it starts behaving and
the more like gold it will become.
>> In what sense?
>> Gold is historically a very stable
asset. doesn't move up and down very
much until recently when you saw nation
states buying gold because they don't
want to hold treasuries. They don't want
to hold dollar denominated assets and
they're viewing gold as a better reserve
asset. People are starting to view
Bitcoin as a very good reserve asset if
Bitcoin's volatility decreases. Right?
No nation state wants to have to go to
report that well you know we have a $500
billion in Bitcoin and there was a 15%
drop in the price of Bitcoin and so we
just lost all this right a politician
would lose their job uh if there was a
15% drop in their reserve assets but if
you're sitting on 500 million$500
billion of gold and it moves 2% nobody's
going to worry about it and I think as
Bitcoin's volatility decreases
um and it adopts more of a traditional
commodity asset type curve.
>> But that's a very long-term view
>> potentially. Yeah. But we're already
starting to see it. Just, you know, look
at the logarithmic power curve, power
law curve, and you'll see kind of it's
starting to flatten. You know, there's
this narrative that retails believe
miners have the power to control Bitcoin
price especially uh around having
because if you don't sell your Bitcoin
then you know the supply and demand
nobody's able to buy more. How do you
comment to that? Is it true? No, it's uh
if you go back two h havingings. Yes.
>> Right. Because the amount of Bitcoin per
block was significant and um miners were
really not in a huddle mode and then
they were selling and then some of them
would huddle. Uh for most of 2024,
all miners were in a full huddle. Now,
in 2025, you're seeing most miners
actually selling their Bitcoin.
>> Now, realize there's only 450 new
Bitcoin issued today. Um, so that's not
a lot. We're still doing a full huddle.
Um, and many of our peers though are
selling, but then you have Michael
Sailor buying 900 Bitcoin a day. So,
you know, miners don't really the the
amount of Bitcoin miners um sell from
new production daily has very little
impact. It's a different story if a
minor like ourselves sitting on
approaching 50,000 Bitcoin. If we decide
to sell 20,000 Bitcoin, yeah, that would
move the market definitely.
>> We have no intention of doing that. By
the way,
>> would you say then your stock should
perform like a Bitcoin treasury company?
>> It does actually. um which is a bad
thing because we're a Bitcoin mining
company and we're not getting value for
the Bitcoin mining business.
>> Uh our stock up until very recently has
been trading a little over one times NAV
of our Bitcoin holdings which means that
our mining business is not getting any
credit. Uh we're now starting to see a
shift in that. Uh you know for example
uh today the stock moved fairly
dramatically and we have been
outperforming Micro Strategy on a daily
basis. Um and I think part of that is um
a little bit how strategy is going about
raising capital today. You know, they're
issuing preferred instruments that have
dividend payments on them. Uh you know,
you saw the Trump family uh convert that
they issued today is fully secured. It's
not an unsecured convert. And so that's
secured by the family assets, the real
estate assets. So I think the market is
starting to price in more risk um into
these deals and it's getting harder and
uh you know the challenge is that if you
have large dividend payments, large
demands on liquidity, you can only
continue if you would by selling equity
in the company or finding some other way
of funding those dividends.
Fore
trading view. My trade GPTch
What do you think caused the price
suppression of Mara stock as well as
some other miners year to date relative
to Bitcoin?
>> I think that's very driven by the AI
story or the lack of an AI story around
certain uh minor stocks. If you look at
um
uh miners like Cipher for example, they
had very positive swing in the beginning
where there was a lot of optimism about
their ability to get an AI customer.
They haven't been able to find an AI
customer and so then the stock started
dipping down. Uh clean spark and mara
have been viewed as kind of mining quasi
mining pure plays. Clean spark yes mara
less so because we also have a
technology business. We also are
beginning um to work with inference at
the edge.
Our model unlike many of the other
miners is we don't want to be a uh an AI
hosting company. We don't want to build
powered shells. Um we also don't want to
provide GPU as a service in the AI
space. We're very focused on providing
inference at the edge as a fully managed
service. And I think that's the area
where the margins and the long-term
revenue streams are much more
attractive. Um, it's a lot more like
Bitcoin mining in some ways, but it also
is you're not dependent on a single or
multiple hosting customers to really
drive your your revenues and it's a lot
less risk from our perspective.
>> A year ago in one of the interviews, you
said Mara is a capital allocator.
>> Um, what's that mean? Well, think of our
name, Mara Holdings. Uh, I have a
background other than being an
entrepreneur in private equity. And it
really comes down to how you allocate
capital. And so, when we look at what
we're going to invest in, we're
constantly weighing, should I spend $500
million in building a new mining site or
should I spend $500 million buying
Bitcoin?
>> Last year, we spent a little over $2
billion buying Bitcoin. Why? Well,
because the middle of last year, we felt
Bitcoin price was going to move very
rapidly upwards. And if you look at the
investment horizon of building a Bitcoin
mining site, it takes you about 12
months to build it until you produce
your first Bitcoin. And then it's going
to take you 18 to 24 months to pay back
that capital. uh if you expect Bitcoin
price to move more rapidly uh in the
short term, you're better off spending
the money just buying Bitcoin, accreting
the value in the upswing of that and
then either leveraging that Bitcoin uh
borrowing against it or generating yield
off it and then using that funds for
other things. And so we're constantly
evaluating how we're investing at the
same time as we're constantly evaluating
how we're raising capital. What's our
average weighted cost of capital? Do we
want to sell equity? Do we want to use
convertible debt? Do we want to use debt
on our assets? Do we want to use project
financing? And project financing hasn't
really been available to Bitcoin miners
because banks weren't open to it. That
is now changing. And I think what we're
going to see is the cost of capital for
Bitcoin miners is going to come down.
The other thing that we've done is we've
now started being very focused on what
we call near zero cost energy. So we
bought a wind farm the end of last year.
uh at that wind farm, we have
essentially zero marginal cost energy.
Whenever the wind blows, that energy
essentially is free because there's no
input cost. There's no gas, there's no
coal, there's no input fuel.
We can take miners that we've already
depreciated fully from a site and we
depreciate our miners over three years
and we can relocate those miners to the
wind farm. They operate only when the
wind blows.
But what that means is that there is
zero capex spend on the miners. There's
zero depreciation on those miners and
there's zero cost for the electricity.
Every time the wind blows and those
miners can run, we're generating Bitcoin
at near zero cost. Over time, as we
retire more and more of our fleet, as we
continue to upgrade it, we'll build a
bigger and bigger percentage of our
fleet that operates not 24 hours a day.
It may operate only five, six, seven
hours a day, but because the energy is
free and the miners have already been
paid for, we don't need a payback in the
same time period. And that makes us much
more capital efficient
because think about it, a large-scale
miner who is grid attached, paying 4.5,
5 cents a kilowatt hour, they are
constantly having to upgrade their
mining fleet, buy the latest equipment
that's most efficient, and then what do
they do with their old miners? They
can't run them at their same sites
anymore. So they have to either sell
them somebody like us maybe or they have
to do something else with them. And so
we believe that you're starting to see
and a great indication of this is look
at the price and the demand for S19
which is now two generations behind
current top of the state-of-the-art
miners. Huge demand in the market for
them. Why would you want to buy a
machine that's two generations old that
has 30 jewels per terahash efficiency
when the current machines are at 15?
Well, it has to be somebody who has near
zero cost energy.
So, we believe that that is the strategy
long term that Bitcoin miners are going
to have to follow. They're going to have
to have near zero cost energy and
they're going to have to really stretch
the life of these assets because
otherwise the capex
uh spinning wheel you're on is just uh
too hard.
>> It sounds like you have the
infrastructure in place to become an AI
data center or operate AI data data
center. Is that something you've
considered?
>> So we're very focused on inference at
the edge which is different. Um the when
people talk about AI data centers today,
they're talking about learning. Uh
learning is not something you get very
well paid for. Um once you've built a
model and you've um you then deploy the
model, you deploy that model in a
different data center where you then do
inference and you need a lot less
compute to do inference because most of
the compute goes into building the
model. Now hyperscalers like Amazon,
Google, Meta, Microsoft, they operate
large um learning data centers that also
do inference at the data center because
they're doing their own proprietary
data.
Now you would think well the
hyperscalers own all the market. It's
not true. About 60% of data center
capacity is still proprietary to the
companies. Why? Because they don't want
to let their data out of the house. JP
Morgan does not let their trading data
out into the public cloud.
>> They do that all in private cloud. They
do it in on-prem near-prem sites. And
when you look at inference AI, which is
if you look at the studies, most of the
revenues from AI will come from
inference, a lot of that inference is
run on a factory floor. It's a system
that controls the manufacturing system.
It's running a model that is constantly
optimizing how that factory is running.
in ekking another little bit of
efficiency out of that factory. And
every night the data from the day is
uploaded into the cloud, a new model is
generated and it's downloaded to the
factory and they do inference at the
site there. The military runs inference
in the field. All this telemetry from
drones that are coming in from radar
systems goes into a data center that's
sitting in a container out in the field.
Um that's inference at the edge. And we
think those are the markets where there
are very good long-term revenue streams
uh where you can build very defensible
notes
as opposed to competing with the
equinexes of the world and those types
of companies.
>> So Mara does mining and also AI. Um for
Bitcoin company there is BPS and for
other companies there EPS. Um how do
investors look at MARA then? It's a lot
of things.
>> Yeah, it's a good point. There are um
many people who are confused a little
bit with what we do. We have those who
are fans of our treasury company model.
There are those who are fans of our
Bitcoin mining model and then there are
fans of uh our technology business and
what we're doing there which is still a
very nent business.
>> So um how do you overcome that? Well,
part of it is you have to communicate
with the investment audience and educate
them. Another thing is we potentially
have to look at things um like segment
reporting. So, separating our treasury
business and the yield we generate off
it etc. from the Bitcoin mining business
in how we report it. Not physically, but
just how we report it so that we can
talk to the different investors in
different ways. Um you could potentially
create a tracking stock for the treasury
business versus the other. Um there a
lot of complex ways to do that which I
don't think necessarily makes sense
today. Um but um you know we view
Bitcoin as the treasury asset we want to
continue to hold. Uh you know right now
uh we're producing quite a lot of
Bitcoin every month and adding to our
stockpile without having to go in the
market and buy it. But if market
conditions change and there's a very
attractive opportunity to buy, then
we're fully prepared to go in and buy
and take advantage of that. and your
cash flow comes from the technology
company.
>> Uh that is the long-term goal today.
That's not enough. And so cash flow
comes from the capital that we raise
through issuing equity.
>> I see.
>> Do you think it makes sense to have a
national Bitcoin miner run by the
government now that we have a Bitcoin
strategic reserve? If I were a
government and I have a mandate, an
executive order now to collect Bitcoin
in a strategic reserve and perhaps even
acquire some in the future, would it not
make sense and just be cheaper to mine
my own?
>> Um, great question. So
four years ago at mining disrupt I gave
a presentation that mining companies
would either become partners with energy
companies or would be owned by energy
companies because Bitcoin miners don't
produce energy and therefore um they're
always going to be paying somebody for
that energy. Um I think we are within
two years of a time where energy
companies truly on a global scale become
partners with Bitcoin miners. This is
electrical energy companies because
there is so much imbalance in the grids
today. Look at what happened in Spain
recently. Um there's so much renewable
energy that is unprofitable.
people have overbuilt renewable energy,
especially in places like Europe, that
there is a now
growing acceptance for Bitcoin mining as
a load balancing strategy for grids,
similar to what you see in Texas. In
Texas, it's not profitable today to
build a peaker plant. It's not
profitable today to build battery
storage because Bitcoin miners do such a
good job at balancing the grid that you
can't do arbitrage on grid energy in the
same way. And so I think what you're
going to see is the revenue neutral way
for the government to generate Bitcoin
for the Bitcoin strategic reserve could
be to use government energy assets,
partner with Bitcoin miners and say, "I
will give you the energy for free.
>> Let's split the Bitcoin."
So it's not a national Bitcoin miner.
>> You'll just get public private
partnership. um not dissimilar to how
the government does government lands and
oil exploration for example.
>> Just on that note, if you ever were to
have a surplus of energy from your wind
farms, would you consider that consider
selling that back to the grid?
>> Absolutely.
>> In a sense,
>> we can't mine Bitcoin with it. We'll
certainly monetize it by selling it to
the grid.
>> Um you started with being a minor and
then you pivot into the technology. Why?
I've been in the technology industry for
40 years. Um, you know, I have touched
everything from
super mini computers, PCs,
semiconductors, internet, dataccoms,
video games,
digital adtech, uh, etc., etc., etc. Um,
I've invested in technology as both a VC
and a private equity, uh, firm. And
Bitcoin mining is an operational
efficiency business. When we started
mining Bitcoin back in 2017, we were an
asset light miner. We bought miners,
rented hosting capacity, plugged in
miners, and ran them. Um, and we used
that strategy because it was the most
capital efficient way of doing business.
It allowed us to grow to be the biggest
in the world. And at the end of 2023, we
then started buying all of our hosting
partners. And we ended up buying 65% of
our hosting partners at less than it
would have cost us to build the sites.
And then in the end of 2024, we started
buying energy assets and we started
mining Bitcoin off of flare gas and oil
fields. So we become more and more of a
vertically integrated on the operations
side. Back in 2021, we realized that we
were too dependent or let me back up for
a second. There are three constraints in
the Bitcoin mining business. We call
them the three C's. Capital, compute,
and capacity. Capital is easy, right?
Compute is rigs, and capacity is power
and a place to put the the miners.
In 2021, the big constraint was compute.
Bit main had a strangle lock on the
market, right? You know, they were
offering miners at
$75
uh per terahash. realize today miners
that are much more powerful are selling
at 17 $18 a terraash. Um, and it hasn't
gotten any cheaper to make them. And so
we believe that at that point we needed
to become technologically vertically
integrated. And so we co-founded a
company called Orodine which is located
in Silicon Valley which today um is the
only US manufacturer of Bitcoin mining
AS6 and has some of the most amazing
technology available and they are now
selling Bitcoin miners but not only
miners they are also selling chips to
people who want to build their own
miners and so now today Mara is becoming
a minor manufacturer. We are building
our own miners. Why? Because we can
build miners specific to our needs and
with certain performance characteristics
that Bitmain and the others can't do.
Why? Because they're not willing to.
We were at one point Bitmain's largest
customer in the world. We've bought very
few miners from them recently. So, we're
very focused on building Orodine as a
way to have a technological edge. We
build our own liquid immersion
technology. Why? because we are of such
scale today that we know exactly what we
want and need and why should I pay
somebody else a margin for something
that I can do myself and so today we
have some very leading edge two-faced uh
liquid immersion technology and we have
other technologies in our technology
business not just firmware orchestration
layer our own pool um you know our
mining pool for example
>> operates um with a luck factor above of
zero, meaning we're positive luck over
long-term periods.
>> What does that mean?
>> Uh so statistically speaking, if you
have 1% of global hash rate, you should
earn 1% of the blocks.
>> Mhm.
>> We earn a little bit more than that.
>> How?
>> Um
let's just say that there's
when you make technology very efficient,
you remove latencies from what you do.
It lets you react faster. And think
about this way that once a block has
been solved, it may be solved in just
under 10 minutes.
>> Ideally, the Bitcoin blockchain, you
know, the the network is constantly
adjusting itself to hit the 10 minutes,
which is why you have the difficulty
increase. The difficulty only changes
every two weeks.
If you're very efficient, you can swap
what your miners are doing from one
block to another block. If a block is
near being solved and you don't think
you will solve it.
>> Oh, I didn't know that. This is cool.
>> Learn something every day. I only have
one more question. Actually, it's
Bonnie's question to Jack Mers. You
asked him about the theoretically
the theoretical possibility of altering
20 the 21 million uh Bitcoin cap if
institutions pressure. Anyway, I'll let
you ask him this question if you want.
It's a good question.
>> Okay. Um I asked Jack Mers the other day
this question about okay in this wild
imagination we all know that you know
Bitcoin is decentralized there's minor
there's nodes of course there's us um
but let's say um a country becomes super
powerful and somehow they acquire half
over half of the miners um find a lot of
you know people that are running the
nodes and try to change the 21 million
cap. Is it possible?
>> Um,
it's not feasible.
Is it possible? China at one point
controlled over 80% of global hash rate.
At the time of the ban, I think it was
71%.
Uh, the US today has about 40% of global
hash rate. Um, it would have to be a
government uh or a group of allies who
could exert enough control through
regulatory means on miners. Uh, in other
words, either go with us or you're out
of business or something similar. Um,
the challenge is the validators, right?
There are a million plus validators out
there who are all very libertarian,
independent in their thinking. And you
know, it's easy to set up a validation
node. You just, it's not a whole Bitcoin
mining center. It's a powerful enough PC
with enough memory and hard drive and
you're up and running. Uh, you know, it
took so long just to get Taproot
approved.
Uh, you know, you already had the block
size wars where 90 plus% of the miners
were in agreement and you still couldn't
get it passed. So, is it feasible? Um, I
think it's very difficult um to have
that happen and I think you would
the value of Bitcoin would drop so pre
precipitously
if it wasn't for the fact that it's a
finite amount. If all of a sudden you
said they're going to now be 210 million
Bitcoin, Bitcoin price would drop by a
factor of 10 possibly.
>> Yeah. And I still cannot think of any
reasons why anybody would do that, but
that's just uh curiosity.
>> Well, you know, sometimes you have to
ask the orthogonal questions to spur
thinking. So, it's a good question.
>> The philosophers of our time are all
Bitcoiners. I told it the other day,
Fred, uh certainly lots of philosophy
for us to uh ponder. Thank you very much
for your time today. Appreciate it.
>> Very welcome. Thank you.
>> Here I go.
>> That mic really likes you. Thank you.
>> All right.